A Guide to the Western Fairfax County Survey Photograph Collection, 1976-1986 (bulk 1985-1986)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: no site, Dunn Loring, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 39-4-A1, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 023
- Tax Map #: 39-4-A1, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 024
- Tax Map #: 39-4-A1, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 025
- Tax Map #: 39-4-A1, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 026
- Tax Map #: 39-4-A1, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 027
- Tax Map #: 39-4-A1, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 028
- Tax Map #: 30-3-A2, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 029
- Tax Map #: 30-3-A2, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 030
- Tax Map #: 30-3-A2, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 031
- Tax Map #: 30-3-A2, Tudor Hall, 1986 March; Roll #: 86-8, Frame #: 032
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 000
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 001
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 002
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 003
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 004
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 005
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 006
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 007
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 008
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 009
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 010
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 011
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 012
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 013
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 014
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 015
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 016
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 017
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 018
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 019
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 020
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 021
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 022
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 023
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 024
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 025
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 026
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 027
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 028
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 029
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 030
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 031
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 032
- Tax Map #: 57-4-A1, Aspen Grove, 1986 April; Roll #: 86-10, Frame #: 033